<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Adcity Mart</string>
    <string name="nav_open" >Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="who_we_are">Around the product. Around the quality. Around the services.\n

        Ad City Mart the name is enough to promote itself. It is a fastest growing company in north india.
        We have 3+ years combined experience from top leading IT companies.\n
        AdCity Mart is a new venture from India, a group of dedicated and talented people.
        We providing services in advertising, direct marketing, design creation, digital marketing and online marketing.
        We have many clients around the world. We shape your dreams and dedicated work on your thoughts and deliver the best.
        Building business on trust and credibility is a principal and the aim of our company.
        Therefore, you can be assured of the best quality services for your business



    </string>
    <string name="mission">To combine techno commercial strategic marketing with quality products and services at competitive
        prices to provide the best IT services to our customers. Profitable growth to all our customer by new creativity and ideas.
        We strive to be the acknowledged global
        leader and preferred partner in helping our clients succeed in the world’s rapidly evolving IT companies.\n
        Our purpose is to enable individuals and businesses to give write information.
        We provide latest marketing information to deliver IT services to our customers.
        We build value for our clients through the strength of our customers’ satisfaction and by consistently producing superior
        operating results. Ad City Mart mission is to generate digital environment.
        Provide the world’s best communications solutions that enable businesses to excel.

        </string>
    <string name="choose">We stand behind the quality of our products and appreciate your business whether it is large or small. We guarantee to make your ordering experience as simple and pleasant as possible.
        We look forward to offering you quality service and products at reasonable prices. </string>
</resources>
